Woman's Building
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Education Programs, 1971-1991, Series 2:; (Box 10-14; 4.9 linear ft.)
  - Extension Program, 1975-1981, 2.3:
    - Goal Attainment Scales, Fall 1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Goal Attainment Scales, Winter 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Goal Attainment Scales, Spring 1981 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Open House, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Publicity, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Skills Check List, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Survey, circa 1977, (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 29-30)
    - Women Writers in Their Homes, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Slide Library, 1975-1990, 2.4:
    - Artist List, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Artist's Resumes, 1987-1988, (8 folders) (Box 13, Folder 33-40)
    - Book Artists, circa 1987 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, December 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Exhibition Slides, circa 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Funding Opportunities, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Grants, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Great American Lesbian Art Show (GALAS), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Publicity and Outreach, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Slide and Video Rental Information, circa 1987 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Slide Catalog, circa 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Slide Lecture and Lists, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Slide Registry, circa 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Slide Submissions, 1988-1990, (6 folders) (Box 14, Folder 1-6)
    - Slides from Anne Gaudlin's Slide Sets, 1975-1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Woman's Building Slide Show Script, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Women Artists of Color, circa 1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Women's Video Center, 1975-1981, 2.5:
    - About Ourselves, By Ourselves, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Andreae Gift, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Articles, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Broadcast Information, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Brochure, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Business Plan, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Funding, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "Cowgirls," circa 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Directors' Biographies, circa 1980 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Equal Time in Equal Space," circa 1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Equipment Contracts, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Equipment Cooperative, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Feminist Media Program, circa 1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Finances, 1975-1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Foreman, Laura, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Funding Sources, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Garden Theatre Festival, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Garden Theatre Festival - Interview with Jerry Langer and Warren Christensen, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Grants, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - History, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - "In Mourning and Rage," 1979 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Legal Issues and Contracts, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Lesbian Tapes Project, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Press Packet Material, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Program Planning, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Projects, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Questionnaire, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Record Companies Drag Their Feet," 1979 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Russell, Philip, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - "Seven (7) Evening of Video By Women," 1977 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - "Single Mothers" Brochure, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Social Art Flyer and Brochure, circa 1979 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Social Art Tapes, circa 1979 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Tour of Video Tapes, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Video Accessibility Project, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Video Artist in Residency Grant, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Video Production Grant, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - The Video Project, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - The Video Project Notebook, circa 1977, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 53-54)
    - The Video Project, Packets for TV Stations, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - The Video Project, "Speak Out" Correspondence, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - "The Waitresses," 1978 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Woman's Building Anniversary Party, Women's Video Extravaganza, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Women's Video, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Workshop with Haline Paul, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Gallery Programs, 1973-1991, Series 3:; (Box 14-20; 5.6 linear feet)
  This series documents the individual visual, performance, literary, and video arts events and exhibitions shown at the Woman's Building. Each event or artist file typically contains correspondence, proposal, artist biography, and publicity material related to the program. The administrative files include comprehensive program development files, financial records, gallery reviews, and surveys.
  The Gallery Programs are arranged into five subseries:
  3.1: Administrative, 1973-1991
  3.2: Exhibits, 1974-1991
  3.3: Performance Art, 1977-1990
  3.4: Literary Arts, 1977-1991
  3.5: Film and Video, 1975-1991
  - Administrative, 1973-1991, 3.1:
    - Ariadne: A Social Art Network, 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 61-62)
    - "Art at the Woman's Building" Statements, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Art Scene Advertisements, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Artist's Gallery Proposals, circa 1983, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 65-66)
    - Artist's Surveys, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Black History Month - Varnette Honeywood, Ruth Waddy, Nathalie Forrest, Doris Davenport, Carroll Parrott Blue, and Barbara McCullough, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Black History Month, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Cable Show Programming, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Calendar, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Commission Art Exhibition Committee, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Community Galleries, 1973-1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1982, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Kathy Clark, Artistic Director, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Thank You Notes, circa 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Calendar, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Fringe Festival, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Gallery and Performance Committees, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Gallery Programs Survey, 1985, (5 folders) (Box 15, Folder 14-18)
    - Gallery Programs Survey Summaries, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Gallery Objectives, circa 1986 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Gallery Reviews, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Gallery Schedule, 1977-1979, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Great American Lesbian Art Show (GALAS), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Guest Register, 1979-1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Insurance, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Insurance, The Art Museum Association, 1976-1977, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Inventory Forms, Completed, 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Lesbian Art Project, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Loan Agreements and Contracts, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Open Wall Gallery, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
    - Open Wall Gallery - Artist's Contracts, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Performance and Conference Series, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Proposal Rejections, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Publicity, circa 1976 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Rental Gallery, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Requests to Perform at the Woman's Building, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Restructuring, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Sample Letters and Forms, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - "These Boots Were Made for Walking" Farewell Party for Cheri Gaulke, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Traveling Exhibitions, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Traveling Exhibitions, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Woman's Community Gallery, circa 1975 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Women's Art Exhibit in City Hall Rotunda, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Women's Art Exhibit in City Hall Rotunda, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
    - Women's Art Exhibit in City Hall Rotunda, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Women's Art Exhibit in City Hall Rotunda, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Exhibits, 1974-1991, 3.2:
    - "Ageless" with Suzanne Lacy, Jerry Allyn, Mihoko Yamagata, Janice DeLoof, Phora Gerdes, Louise Rothman, and Tressa Prisbey, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
    - Alt, Marlene, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Anatomy of Worship" by Deborah Kruger and Cheri Gaulke, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Artist as Shaman," 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Artist as Shaman," Artists' Biographies, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Artists Contributing to the Solution (ACTS), 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
    - Basket Exhibit, Pat Hickman and Lillian Elliott, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "The Beastiary," 1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Bedtime Stories: A Multi-Media Installation" by Anna Homler and Joyce Wexler-Ballard, circa 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "Beyond the Feminity of Eileen Gray," 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Billboard Project, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Break the Silence: Finding Our Voices," 1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Broken Heart Art," 1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Broken Heart Art" Loan Agreements, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "The Bus Poster Project," 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Catlett, Elizabeth, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - "Contemporary Women Artists," 1986 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - "Cross Pollination," 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
    - "Cross Pollination" Artists' Information, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - "Cross Pollination" Poster Distribution, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 24-25)
    - "Crossing Cultural Boundaries," 1989, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 26-28)
    - "Current Wave: An International Exhibition of Women's Posters," 1984 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "The Day of the Dead," 1990, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
    - "A Day Without Art," 1989 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Demanche, Michel, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - "Earth Vision/Human Scale" with Dinah Berland, Vida, Laurie Brown, and Marilyn Bridges, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - "East Meets West" with Mineko Grimmer and Hilary Baker, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - "Family Album," 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Family Album" Finances, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ficara, Robin, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Food is Art/Art is Food," 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Frese, Linda, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "From History to Action: An Exhibition in Celebration of the Tenth Anniversary of the Woman's Building," 1984, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Gamboa, Diane, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Gentlemen's Choice, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
    - "Gentlemen's Choice" Typesetting, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Giordano, JoAnn, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Glass Show, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Goldman, Laurie, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "Guilding the Building," 1990, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - "Having Our Cake" - 15th Anniversary Birthday Cake, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
    - Hendrick, Rebecca, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Hildebrand, Kari, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Hoge, Virginia, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - "Holiday Party," 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    - "Image and Text," 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
    - "Inside/Outside," 1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Khmer/Cambodian Exhibitions, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Korean Women Artists, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Kusama, Yayoi, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - "The Last Lunch" by Ellen Lampert, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Lawrence, Deborah, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Larrari, Margaret, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - "Lesbian Fantasies" by Nancy Fried, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - "Letter Forms" by Gilan Hirsch, Anna Homler, and Devorah Jackson, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Liu, Hung, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Maurer, Laura, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Mazer, June L., 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Membership Exhibition for 15th Anniversary of Woman's Building, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 39-40)
    - Millett, Kate, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Murdock, Maureen, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - "Naked Ladies" by Kate Millett, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Native American Show, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Open Wall Prints and Drawings Show, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - "The Postcard Project: Celebrating our Heroines," 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - "Postcards by Women," 1983 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Prier, Carol Molly, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - "Public/Private Herstory" with Portland McCormick, Cat Ashworth, Susan Kerr, and Dianne Malley, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - "Quest for Balance" by Marsia Alexander, Barbara Magnus, and Echiko Ohira, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - "Reading the Personal, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - "Reflections on Survival," 1987, (3 folders) (Box 17, Folder 52-54)
    - Roberts, Gail, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Aminah, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Rosenblum, Nancy, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Saar, Betye, circa 1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "Santa Barbara Artists," 1990, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
    - Siskin, Sharon, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Small, Deborah, circa 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - "Sounding Patterns," 1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Spirit Guides," 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - "Spirit Guides" - Thank yous to Artists, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - "Sums of the Parts," 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Swirnoff, Lois, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "Taking Liberties," 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - "Textiles as Texts: Arts Among Hmong Women from Laos," 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
    - Thomas, Morgan, circa 1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - "Through Darkness to Light," 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - "Through the Looking Glass," 1990 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "Toys in Babeland," 1989, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
    - "Toys in Babeland," Artist Information, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
    - "Until That Last Breath: Women with AIDS," 1988-1989, (4 folders) (Box 18, Folder 24-27)
    - "Until That Last Breath: Women with AIDS," Contributions, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Valentine's Show, circa 1985 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Van Syoc, Jere, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - "Visionary Landscapes," 1987 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - "Visionary Landscapes," Loan Agreements, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - "Viva la Vida: An Homage to Frida Kahlo," 1987 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - "Ways with Wood," 1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - "What is Feminist Art," 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - "When Beauty is Enough" by Ann Page and Phyllis S. Muldavin, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Wilson, Millie, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Women of Chouinard, circa 1974 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - "Women Photographers in America," 1985 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Women's Caucus Show, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - "Women in American Architecture: An Historic and Contemporary Perspective," 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - "Women in American Architecture: An Historic and Contemporary Perspective," Correspondence (A-Z), 1977-1978, (3 folders) (Box 18, Folder 42-44)
    - "Women in American Architecture: An Historic and Contemporary Perspective," Finances, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Performance Art, 1977-1990, 3.3:
    - Anderson, Jamie, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - "Artists Choose Artists," 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Bedroom Stories" by Anna Homler and Joyce Wexler-Ballard, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bienvenue, Marcella, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - "Bleeding Rose" by Henry Hoffman, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - "Comedy Night," 1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - "Confess to the Powers That Be" by Marla Myers, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - "Danceworks" by Gilberte Meunier, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - "Femina: An Intraspace Voyage," 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Forti, Simone, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - "Funk Lessons" with Adrian Piper, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Gorman-Jacobs, Judy, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Hassinger, Maren, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Higby, Sha Sha, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - International Women's Day, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - "Love Novellas" by Jerri Allyn, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Maguire, Terrill, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Manley, Beatrice, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Mersky, Kres, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Mother Art, Feminist Art Workers, and The Waitresses, circa 1978-1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - "Natural History: Telling More About the Unknown Animals" by Liebe Gray, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Nemec, Vernita, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - "No Frills," 1986 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - "An Oral Herstory of Lesbianism," 1979 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "An Oral Herstory of Lesbianism," Photographs, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Rime," A Poetry and Dance Company, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Ringgold, Faith, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Sun, May, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - "Tall Wheat" by Susan Banyas, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - "Trenzas: The Braids of Frida Kahlo," 1989 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - "The Waitresses," 1977-1984 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - "The Whale Concerts" by Liebe Gray, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Wolf, Sara, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - "Me and My Shadow" by Terry Wolverton, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Women's Coffeehouse Collective, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - "The Wonderful World of Betty" by Leslie Belt and Bia Lowe, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Literary Arts, 1977-1991, 3.4:
    - Atwood, Margaret, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Bernikow, Louise, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Braverman, Kate, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Coleman, Wanda, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - "Dark and Bright Fires," 1976 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Exposures: Women and Their Art Book Signing, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - French, Marilyn, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Griffin, Susan, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - "Inside Out" - A Multi-Cultural Performance of Dramatic Monologues, Poetry, and Fiction by Asian-American Women Writers, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Lifson, Martha, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - MacDonald, Barbara and Cynthia Rieh, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Moore, Honor, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - "Mosaic Voices: A Transcultural Series of Readings by Nationally Known and Local Writers," 1987 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Parker, Pat, circa 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Publicity, circa 1984 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Readings, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Rich, Adrienne and Mary Daly, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Sarton, May, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - "Spoken Word" by Linda J. Albertano, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - "Taking Risks" with Judith McDaniel, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Women for All Seasons, Drafts, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 58-59)
    - Women for All Seasons, Final Copy, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Women for All Seasons, Production, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 61-62)
    - Women for All Seasons, Writer Entries, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 63-64)
    - Women Writers Series, 1980, 1983, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 65-66)
    - "Women's Spirit" Reading, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Film/Video, 1975-1991, 3.5:
    - "The Bell Jar," Event Publicity, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - "The Bell Jar," Film Industry Publicity, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - "The Bell Jar," Fundraising, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - "The Bell Jar," Fundraising, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "The Bell Jar," Photographs, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Cate Video Project, circa 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Committed" with Sheila McLaughlin, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "Divine Horsemen: The Living Gods of Haiti" by Maya Deren, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "An Evening of Lesbian Films" with Barbara Hammer, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "Eyes on Art," 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "Eyes on Art" Budget, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "Eyes on Art" Proposals, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - "Friday the 13th Video Night," 1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - "The Incredible Shrinking Woman," 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "I've Heard the Mermaids Singing," 1988 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Incest Awareness Project, 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
    - Iris Films, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Light, Allie, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - LA Freewaves Event with Shu Lea Chang, Graham Dent, Melissa Chang, and Valerie Soe, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Los Angeles Women's Video Festival, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 18-19)
    - "Moonlight" by Kayt Schneider, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - "The Mothers of Plaza de Mayo," 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Performance Artists Make Videos, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - "Putting Our Hands to Other Labor: The Women's Art Movement in Southern California," 1986 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - "Quilts and Women's Lives" by Pat Ferrero, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - "Video Mosaic" with Alile Larkin, Su-Chen Hung, Melody Ramirez, and Valerie Soe, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Video Proposals, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Walsh, Alida, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Women's Graphic Center, circa 1976-1989, Series 4:; (Box 20-23, 32-50; 5.6 linear feet)
  The Women's Graphic Center series document the business activities related to the operation of the Center, including customer contracts and bids, finances, and strategic planning. The series also includes documentation on the typesetting and graphic design classes offered by the Center staff. The artist's and general projects files contain examples of art and printing work done at the Center by staff, students or outside artists. Files are arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
  The Women's Graphic Center files are arranged into 3 subseries:
  4.1: Administrative, circa 1979-1988
  4.2: Artist's Projects, circa 1976-1989
  4.3: General Projects, circa 1976-1989
  - Administrative Files, circa 1979-1988, 4.1:
    - Bids and Contracts, A-B, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Bids and Contracts, C, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Bids and Contracts, D-F, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Bids and Contracts, G-I, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Bids and Contracts, J-L, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Bids and Contracts, M-O, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Bids and Contracts, P-R, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Bids and Contracts, S-T, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Bids and Contracts, U, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Bids and Contracts, V-W, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Bids and Contracts, Y-Z, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Bids and Contracts, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Brochure, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Brochure Copy, circa 1979 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Budget, Analysis of Finances, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Budget, Paid Invoices, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 43)